AHMED A. IDHAIR

Android Developer & Flutter Developer

Email · ahmed.idhair213@gmail.com Whatsapp . 00970597639981

PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am an experienced specialist in the field of Android Application Development and Flutter Application Development, successfully completed more than 20 projects.

I have expert skills in the field of Android Full Stack development and Flutter Development. I work clearly, qualitatively and quickly.

CAREER HISTORY

JAN 2016 -FEB 2017	
ANDROID APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER, ISO	OFT

Responsible for monitoring Android applications development.

• Design and build advanced applications for the Android platform.

Works:-

✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.taktakah

JAN 2017 -FEB 2018

ANDROID APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER, SPACE

- Responsible for monitoring Android applications development.
- Design and build advanced applications for the Android platform.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.
- Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general

Works:-

- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=space.ps.test
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=space.ps.testary
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=space.ps.dooz
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=arn.ps.ajyal

APRIL 2018 – JUNE 2019

ANDROID APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER, HEXA

- Responsible for monitoring Android applications development.
- Design and build advanced applications for the Android platform.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.
- Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general

Works:-

✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hexa.enjaze

JAN 2020 - PRESENT

ANDROID APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER, SMART ORIENTATION

- Responsible for monitoring Android applications development.
- Design and build advanced applications for the Android platform.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features
- Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general

Works:-

- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gph.manaretharamain
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gph.umrahapp
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.soe.maharat
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.vegas.smarthaji
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.soe.yaduser
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.soe.yadstore
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.vegas.mkanak
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.soe.dialect
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.soe.ucs
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.vegas.mo3edat
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.vegas.cusmo3edat
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.soe.qasedoun

Other Works Freelancer:-

- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=om.zaad.buy
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=om.zaad.seller
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.osoolsystem.osool
- ✓ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=ae.benchmark.findmytruck

EDUCATION

```
2014 - 2016
UNIVERSITY COLLEGE OF APPLIED SCIENCES (UCAS)
ANDROID APP DEVELOPMENT
```

SKILLS

- Android SDK
- Java & Kotlin
- Dart
- Local Databases (Realm, Sqlite, Hive (Flutter), sqflite (Flutter))
- Gps Tracking
- Design Patterns (MVP, MVVM, MVC)
- Firebase
- SQLite
- UX UI
- Fetch data Network
- Social Login
- Payment SDK
- Github
- GitLab
- Bitbucket